

CONTACT

Buenos Aires, Argentina

© chotsourian.marcos@gmail.com

2 +54 9 11 2453 9566

19/06/1991

im Linked In

Portfolio and resources

EDUCATION

2022

Training in active pedagogy oriented to FullStack Bootcamps

SIMPLON

Sevilla, Spain

2021

C# Basic, Intermediate and

Advanced

Udemy

Buenos Aires, Argentina

2021

Bootcamp FullStack: .NET + Angular **NEORIS**

Buenos Aires, Argentina

2020

Professional Webmaster

UTN

Buenos Aires, Argentina

2018

Philosophy Superior Teacher

UBA

Buenos Aires, Argentina

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native

English - Proficient

French - Intermediate

WORK SAMPLE

My Notes is a simple and scalable website in which you can organise your own personal notes!

You can review the code in the repositories below.

The site is actually running in Heroku.

BackEnd Repo My Notes

Site My Notes

MARCOS CHOTSOURIAN

Ssr FullStack Dev

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Having dedicated many years to different education projects, I decided to work also in programming and computer sciences. I started as a DBA and then continued as a Full Stack Web Developer and Integrator Developer. Later on, I became a FullStack teacher on employability oriented courses. I am strong in back-end, algorithms, team work and communication skills. I am now working as a freelance FullStack Dev.

SKILLS

- .NET
- Entity Framework
- SQL

React

TypeScript

JavaScript

- API REST
- GIT
- MVC
 - Layered Architechture Scrum
- Agile
 - Layered Architechture
 - Organized
 - HTMLCSS
 - Bootstrap
- IndependentReliable
- Bootstrap

WORK HISTORY

June 2023 - now

Freelance Fullstack Developer

Delivering web sites in .NET Core + Entity Framework + ReactTS

October 2022 - June 2023

FullStack Teacher, Fundación Don Bosco, Spain

- Designed roadmap, content and resources for a six-month intensive FullStack Bootcamp.
- Final projects were presented with .NET Core and ReactJS.
- Acted as Team Leader in real-job simulation for the students all along.
- Implemented Agile and Scrum methodologies.

July 2022 - October 2023

Integrator Developer, SG Fintech, Argentina

- Setting up, carrying and testing integration processes with clients.
- Developed features according to client's customs requirements.
- Developed fixes according to bugs and improvements needed.
- Worked side by side with Functional Analysts and QA Testers.
- Developed SQL scripts to track down unusual or unexpected operations.

July 2021 - May 2022

FullStack Developer, NEORIS, Argentina

- Worked within a huge project and framework migrating web sites of an administration system.
- Migrated web sites from .NET Web Forms to .NET MVC and KnockoutJS.
- Worked with Agile and Scrum methodologies.

October 2020 - July 2021

DBA, Comisión Nacional de Valores, Argentina

- Developed SQL scripts for data gathering and analysis.
- Elemental database maintenance.